(Sheldon(off):)I'm going to need a larger shirt.
(Sheldon(off):)This one's a little tight under the arms.
(Howard(Picks up receiver):)Okay.
(Leonard:)Maybe it's tight because
you're wearing long underwear?
(Sheldon:)Yes, of course that's why it's tight.
(Leonard:)Let me rephrase the question.
(Leonard:)- Why are you wearing long underwear?
- You're kidding.
(Sheldon:)Shouldn't the question be,
why aren't you?
No, it should be, why are you?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, these rental tuxedos...
(Sheldon:)...have been worn by hundreds
of sweaty strangers.
l don't like my own sweat
touching my skin.
(Sheldon:)How do you think I feel about theirs?
- Why don't you slip this on?
- Said the hangman offering a noose.
Heh, well, that wasn't as entertaining
as when he rents bowling shoes...
(Raj:)...but it was right up there.
(Howard:)Well, that's it.
My orders have been rescinded.
l am officially "no go" to space.
I'm sorry, Howard, but I gotta tell you,
I'm a little relieved you're not going.